

Jakob Wahlers

813-409-8384 Jaywahlers@gmail.com Tampa, FL 33602

SUMMARY

Through any situation, if taught properly I will follow and respect rules as well as put my best foot forward in my work and work ethic. I have a passion for the environment as well as science as a whole and would love nothing more than to go forward in each field and look for new opportunities to learn. I have lots of experience with the environment and have worked lots of part time jobs since I was 15, but more recently a couple of years with slightly higher stressed situation handling as well as being given better responsibilities within work. Am willing to work hard and learn new skills and contribute to a team environment and lead in the right direction if needed.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Bachelor of Arts: Geography and Geographic Information Systems University of South Florida Expected in Dec 2023

Tampa, FL

Associate of Arts: General Studies

Hillsborough Community College Dec 2020

Tampa, FL

- Research: Economics and Geography.
- Research: Nightlife in Tampa and Channelside through Urban Planning Courses. And through data collecting while interviewing lots of people in the area.
- Additional Coursework in Research Methods and Fieldwork.
- Additional Coursework in Field Methods through River sampling and substrate classification through microscopes in order to determine the health of a somewhat aquatic environment. (Dried out riverbed at the time).
- Data collection of a couple wetlands by classifying flora and fauna as well as
 determining where the wetland ends and begins based off of tree waterlines,
 tree height, and soil sample taking throughout the area.

EXPERIENCE

Landmark Surveyor/Rodman

Landmark Surveying and Engineering Co.

Tampa, FL

- -Current Job
 - Measuring
 - Using surveying equipment and tools
 - Plotting areas/points
 - Finding property corners and setting them
 - Doing basic construction/builder's work

Plaza Member

Amalie Arena - Home of The Tampa Bay Lightning/ Jan 2023 to Current Tampa, FL

- -Current Job
 - Helping people with information about the arena/area

Helping plaza members with different tasks

Concierge and Access Control

Towers of Channelside/Jan 2019 to Aug 2022

Tampa, FL

- Problem solving
- Customer service
- Security

Cashier and Barista

Starbucks/ Mar 2018 to Aug 2019

Tampa, FL

- Making drinks
- Customer service

Front Service Clerk

Publix/ Mar 2010 to Jul 2017

Tampa, FL

• Every job in Publix from customer service to bagging to counting money in the back office.

SKILLS

- Guest Experiences
- Proper Equipment Operation
- Food Safety Procedures
- Company Policies and Procedures
- Point of Sale (POS) System Operations
- Excel knowledge
- Leadership
- Team player

- ARC GIS skills and understanding
- People Skills
- Computer Skills
- PPE Use
- Planning & Organizing
- Reliable Team Worker
- Fast Learner